The radiance of the night shines through my window
but the path to immortality is long.
The Eight Views and Nine-Bend Streams are desolate.
Living beings question the miseries of the world over a jar of wine.
Forget about Nirvana and rebirth,
I will break through the waves with my own flesh and blood.
The heavens are vast, so what if I was born mediocre ?
I stare at the Dao in my moments of madness
as the storm rages just below.
I've been thinking about life and death in my dreams.
I've unsheathed my sword to ask the immortals
why the world is a-changing.
Heaven and earth reveals its poignant truths.
Swallow the Four Seas and the Eight Wastelands,
experience all the vicissitudes of life in an instant.
I will defy the light in the sky
to continue to write a new chapter for all things in the three realms of existence.
Just a thought separates mortal from immortal.
Transform your insignificant body into light.
The hardships of the journey
will temper this young man's heart.
If I become a Renegade Immortal, will I hesitate to fight the heavens ?
Renegade Immortal\NSubtitles by Bonobosubs\Nhttps://discord.gg/Ceckd4pdVA
This person has been chasing me all the way from Zhao
and I still can't determine his cultivation level.
Even if you have the stones to operate the teleportation formation,
Na Duo\NFive Elements Planet's cultivator\NEarly stage Soul Transformation
do you think you can escape ?
What a powerful Divine Sense !
After a single attack,
my Nascent Soul is already at the brink of collapse.
What's...
his cultivation level ?
His power feels familiar...
Could it be ?
This cannot continue,
I cannot let him take the initiative,
cause if he does, I will die.
I need to fight back to survive.
His flag isn't finished.
If he finishes is, it will trigger a tribulation.
I didn't expect
to find this kind of artifact
on this waste of a planet.
Fortunately, before this trip,
I refined another nearly-finished restriction flag.
Looks like it can threaten him.
Senior has been following me
with great killing intent.
What does Senior want from me ?
If my cultivation was at its prime,
this would be easy.
But I only recovered 30% of my power...
if I fight a tribulation now, I will get hurt again.
Junior, give me the bag you found in the Land of the Ancient God.
The Land of the Ancient God ?
Is this what Senior wants ?
That's right.
In the past,
I got seriously injured.
So I went to the Land of the Ancient God to find treasures to help me recover.
I got into some trouble there.
The Blood Sea Warriors chased me
so in order to safeguard my findings,
I had no other choice
but to hide my bag of holding.
I wanted to take it back later.
But as you know,
it ended up in your hands.
I have returned the bag to you,
I will now take my leave.
Stop !
Little friend,
don't be rash !
Why did Senior go back on his word ?
Was the red lightning you used before
the Ji Realm ?
Junior, you really are full of surprises.
Not only do you have a treasure that can attract a tribulation
but you also have the Ji Realm.
If Senior doesn't have anything else
then Junior will take his leave.
Do you want to breakthrough your Ji Realm bottleneck ?
Little friend,
do you know what this is ?
Ji Realm ?
On my home planet,
it's called the Five Colored Ji Realm.
This wasn't originally mine.
It was gifted to me by a friend
as he was dying.
You remind me of him.
In the whole Cultivation Alliance,
Ji Realm cultivators are very rare.
I cannot tell the properties of your Ji Realm
but I know how you can breakthrough.
The Cultivation Planet Crystal is given
to a country when it reaches rank 6.
The old monsters of the Cultivation Alliance use their powers
to form the crystal.
It's a rank 6 cultivation country's national treasure.
If you obtain and refine it,
you can breakthrough your Ji Realm.
If you obtain the crystal and get the qualifications
to leave this waste of a planet
you can come find me on the Five Elements Planet,
my name is Na Duo.
Luckily, I managed to avoid this fight.
If I can reach Soul Transformation
then I may have a chance to get the Cultivation Planet Crystal
to breakthrough my Ji Realm.
But for now,
I need to reach Soul Formation.
Understanding the heavens
is crucial for that.
But I have spent my whole life
following the demonic path.
If I want to breakthrough,
there is only one way:
Wang Lin's avatar\NEarly stage Nascent Soul
becoming a mortal.
Four Sect Alliance
The Four Sect Alliance
is a rank 4 cultivation country.
Lu Xing
Let's rest here.
Go ahead.
Alright.
Sir, are you passing by or staying ?
I see that you carry medicinal herbs in your backpack.
I wonder if Brother
could possibly be a traveling doctor ?
I am Lu Xing.
Brother,
do you have any medicine
to cure the evil wind. (regular cold)
Is someone sick ?
A servant girl is sick.
We are still 7 days away from the capital
and the medecine prescribed by the doctor
isn't very effective.
Perhaps...
this is my opportunity to enter the mortal world.
Please lead the way.
Please.
Brother,
just look from here,
there is no need to go inside.
Please stretch out your hand.
She clearly isn't a servant, but the master.
Poison ?
Have her eat it raw, she will be cured by tomorrow.
This...
This looks like an ordinary willow tree leaf.
I'm afraid this guy isn't a doctor.
He is clearly a lunatic.
A hundred-years old willow leaf !
I don't know how to consume it.
Is there any trick to using this leaf ?
Eating it raw is fine.
I didn't expect that in just 400 years,
I could accumulate so much killing intent.
I killed way too many people...
If I allow this aura to grow,
over time,
it will corrupt my Dao Heart.
The killing intent can be domineering
and used for spells.
But if I want to turn into a mortal
it will ententually dissipate.
It's a pity...
The best I can do is condense it.
That's fine.
Hey Brother,
your leaves are really magical.
My daught-
My servant feels much better.
Come on,
let's toast !
It's been a long time since I drank with someone.
Come on, cheers !
Old man,
I've heard you talk about Xing Fen Tower countless times.
Enough.
This time,
I will see if you're just bragging.
Go ahead.
You'll be drunk soon anyway.
I'll wait for you to pass out and I'll start.
No...
You...
Let's toast for him !
What a drinker !
Come, cheers!
You should drink less, we have to keep guard.
It's been a long time
since I saw this side of Life.
Today, without noticing,
I absorbed spiritual energy extremely fast.
Wang Lin's avatar\NMiddle stage Nascent Soul
It made me breakthrough to the Middle stage already.
It seems that distancing myself from cultivation
to become a mortal
is the right path.
Now, I will dance for you guys.
Let's have fun !
Have fun ?
Am I making a fool of myself ?
Of course you are !
Look over here !
Quality woven clothes !
Cold powder ! Cold powder !
Brother Wang,
don't keep staring at them.
If you are noticed, we will be troubled.
Brother Lu,
what are these black pillars ?
Those are Immortal pillars.
This place is my country's capital
so it's protected by Immortals, hence the Immortal pillars.
There are Immortals living inside the pillars.
Although they are merely Foundation Establishment,
it's rare to protect the mortal world like that,
very rare.
I didn't expect you to know so much about Immortals.
What's the meaning of the Four Sect Alliance ?
There are 4 cultivation sects
in our country.
The righteous and virtuous White Cloud Sect.
The Water Ink Sect, with its bustling rivers and waterfalls.
The Green Wood Sect, blessed by the sky and the earth.
And the Black Soul Sect, hidden in darkness.
These 4 sects are relatively independent.
They each collect disciples in the mortal world.
Whenever there's a big event, they cooperate.
That's why it's called the Four Sect Alliance.
To be honest,
my dream was to become an Immortal.
But the crown prince was so kind to me.
If it weren't for that,
I might have become an Immortal.
I heard that cultivation depends on talent and opportunity.
It's not something you decide.
Life is short.
It's better to be happy here.
You know me well Brother !
Brother Lu,
let's part ways here.
The young lady asked me to thank you.
Here are 10 taels of gold,
consider it your payment.
Note: 1 tael = 37.5g
Thank you.
Spoiler
You old pervert !
You came to my shop to see the women changing their clothes ?
Deserved !
At such an age, how could you be so lewd ?
I'll hit you every time I see you !
Get lost !
I'll beat you to death !
Alright.
Hey
young man,
your forehead is wide,
(Note: sign of luck, talent)
energy envelops your body,
you must be special !
I've hidden my cultivation.
This person is just a mortal,
he cannot see through me.
If no one guides you,
I'm afraid you will never reach Soul Formation.
What a pity !
How pitiful...
Who are you ?
You don't need to know who I am.
But I know how to make you reach Soul Formation.
Senior,
please teach me.
I'm getting old.
The moment I get hungry,
I can't remember anything.
I know a very good restaurant.
Let's go there and talk while we eat.
Delicious !
It smells so good.
Bring me another duck !
And 2 jars of wine !
Try some, it's so good.
Tell me.
How can I reach Soul Formation ?
This, it's easy.
Wait until I finish eating this piece
This old man is really strange.
He can see through my cultivation.
If it's not a coincidence,
then his cultivation
must be at least Soul Formation.
The Soul Formation stage requires one to understand the heavens
but I believe you already know that.
In addition,
to reach Soul Formation
you must form your own...
domain.
Do you know what a domain is ?
Young man,
reflect on this.
Once you comprehend what a domain is,
you won't be far from Soul Forma...
...tion
I need to use the restroom.
Let's continue when I get back.
Young man,
your forehead is wide,
energy envelops your body,
you must be special !
Go away.
What a pity...
If no one guides you,
I'm afraid you will never reach Core Formation.
Who are you ?
You don't need to know who I am.
This old man
doesn't scam randomly.
Young man,
if no one guides you,
I'm afraid you will never reach Nascent Soul.
You don't need to know who I am.
Let's find a place to relax
and have a good time.
Okay.
Young man,
how long do you plan to rent ?
This is the craft of our family.
Look carefully.
Tie Zhu won't work with you in the future.
When I save enough money
you will go to the capital
to become an official.
Young man, look.
There's a garden in the back.
Although this shop has been empty for many years
and is dirty,
you should have everything you need.
I take it.
This much ?
The place is yours then !
You won't catch me !
Wait a second !
I'm sure I can catch you !
No you won't  !
Be careful,
don't make trouble.
Hidden from the world
in a city of mortals.
Far away for the bloody cultivation path,
living life as a mortal.
Maybe,
this is really the way to understand the heavens.
Old man,
what do you want to do tonight ?
Nascent Soul...
Middle stage Nascent Soul ?
Should I help him ?
As I mentioned before in the note of episode 32, the story of that bag of holding differs between the donghua and the novel. Na Duo was cultivating in the War God Shrine a technique to absorb the death energy of corpses. He was severly injured in combat and was recovering from his injuries there for thousands of years and Wang Lin stole his bag while he was uncounscious in his corpse state.\N\NThe explanation of "I hid it there for later" makes very little sense. When you know that Na Duo was so heavily injured that he literally became a corpse in a sect's graveyard in order to recover, the donghua's explanation pales in comparison.
I've had my share of wounds,
now I want to fight back.
Is my destiny a wall of restrictions
that's blocking all my hopes
for life ?
My flesh and blood witnessed the past,
my adversity pushed me to brave the waves.
How do you navigate through the years passing by ?
Nirvana and rebirth are no longer
out of reach.
Immortals
are obsessed with delusions of grandeur.
Renegades
seek to crush the impermanence of the heavens.
Don't tell me that I overestimate myself
and that the path to revenge leads to hell
because I don't see the harm in that.
My new body opens its eyes
and awakens from its dream.
I have overcome many trials
to get this body back.
No matter how many endless dark nights go by,
I can still see.
By sticking to this thought, I will get it done
by my own hands.
Returning to my body opened my eyes,
I need to continue my Immortal journey.
With a flick of a finger,
only my indomitable heart remains.
Life and death trials temper me, I am not afraid of losing my soul.
Even if there are countless tribulations and hardships.
Overcome this fate, smash through the obstacles,
like the descent of a god.